roberthalf.com.au 2010-11-29

# Privacy statement

Welcome to [www.roberthalf.com.au](http://www.roberthalf.com.au/) (the "Site"). This website privacy policy ("Policy") describes how Robert Half Australia Pty Limited ( **ABN 32 081 257 052** ) ("We", "we", or "RHA") may use and disclose Personal Information that we may collect about you through the Site. In this Policy, "Personal Information" refers to information or an opinion, whether true or not and whether recorded in a material form or not, about a natural person whose identity is apparent, or can reasonably be ascertained, from the information or opinion.

**Collections and Uses of Personal Information  
**When you use or register with the Site, we may ask for certain Personal Information that will assist us to provide you with a service that meets your needs and circumstances. The categories of Personal Information we may request include your name and contact information (email, address and phone number). Depending on the nature of your inquiry or activities on the Site, we may also ask for your job search criteria and preferences, your employment experience, educational history, your skills, references information, background information, and other information contained in your resume, and any RHA login ID and password created by you. For candidates who have previously been registered with or worked for RHA, such persons may enter, at their discretion, their employee ID to facilitate the registration process.  

If you do not provide such information, RHA may not be able to provide you with access to or full use of sections of the Site or with any other services you request.  

The Site also utilises cookies to track your online activities, including, but not limited to, registration, submissions, and information requests. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to your computer's hard disk for record keeping purposes. Most web browsers are set to accept cookies. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's browser. If you do not wish to receive any cookies you may set your browser to refuse cookies. This may mean you will not be able to take full advantage of the services on the Site.  

After your successful registration with the Site, you will be able to access, review and change your Personal Information through the Review Profile feature of the Site. If at any time you wish to delete your Personal Information from the Site, please contact us by sending a message to the email address below. We will take reasonable steps to delete information in response to such a request.  

We use Personal Information and other data collected through the Site in order to meet the needs of our business, including: to register you with the Site; to provide you with information regarding employment opportunities and career-related information; and to otherwise provide you with requested information or services.  

We may also from time to time use your Personal Information to send you automated email messages or marketing materials regarding our services, including employment information. You may opt out of receiving such marketing email messages by sending a message to the email address below. Please allow 5 business days for this request to be processed.  

RHA will not use or disclose any information about you without your consent, unless the use or disclosure is:

  1. for the purpose of disclosing information to our clients where necessary and appropriate in connection with the provision of a service to you;
  2. for the purpose of disclosing information to companies and individuals we employ to perform business functions and services on our behalf, on the basis that such companies and individuals must protect your Personal Information and may not disclose or use it for unrelated purposes. Such functions may include, for example, hosting our Web servers, analysing data, providing legal, accounting and marketing services;
  3. to the extent necessary or appropriate to government agencies, advisors, and other third parties in order to comply with applicable laws, the service of legal process, or if we reasonably believe that such action is necessary to (a) comply with the law requiring such disclosure; (b) protect the rights or property of RHA or its affiliated companies; (c) prevent a crime or protect national security (d) protect the personal safety of the users or the public;(e) to assist the investigation of an offence by a law enforcement authority; or prevent a serious or  imminent threat to an individual's life, health or safety or public health or safety.

RHA will endeavour to take reasonable steps to keep secure any information which we hold about you. You should note that the internet is not a secure method of transmitting information and, as such, we are not responsible for the security of any information sent or received over the internet. Furthermore, RHA may disclose and you consent to such disclosure of Personal Information to RHA servers and electronic systems located outside the country where you are located. This is due to RHA using overseas facilities to store, process or back up its information. However, this does not change our commitment to keep your information secure.

**Revisions to the Policy  
**By providing us with your Personal Information you agree that your data may be transferred and processed outside Australia.  
If we change this privacy policy we will post any updates here for your review. If we change material terms in this Policy, we will provide notice of the revised policy for 30 days on the home page at [www.roberthalf.com.au](http://www.roberthalf.com.au/) with a link back to this page. The amended Policy will apply between us whether or not we have given you specific notice of any change.  
This Policy is effective as of October 18, 2010. If you have any questions about our website privacy policies, please contact us at:

_The Webmaster  
Robert Half Australia Pty Ltd  
Level 45, MLC Centre, 19 Martin Place  
Sydney NSW 2000  
Email Address:_ [_reactionsau@RHA.net_](mailto:reactionsau@RHA.net)
